Contact

1luster1ec@comcast.net

www.linkedin.com/in/eillen-luster-msn-rn-ccrn-b1b70388 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care

Healthcare

Healthcare Management

Certifications

Critical Care Registered Nurse

Honors-Awards

2015 Houston Chroncle Top 100 Oustanding Nurses of Houston

2013 Bronze Awardee Good Samaritan Foundation

Presidential Award

Item Panel Reviewer for NCLEX

NCSBN Strategic Analysis Research Panel

Eillen Luster, MSN, RN, CCRN

Program Coordinator at cHI st . Luke's Vintage Hospital Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the higher education industry. Skilled in Microsoft Excel, Management, Critical Care, Hospitals, and Healthcare. Strong professional with a Master's Degree focused in Nursing Leadership and Management from Western Governors University.

Experience

cHI st . Luke's Vintage Hospital
Program Coordinator
February 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months)

Ben Taub General Hospital Nurse Manager September 2011 - June 2017 (5 years 10 months)

Education

Western Governors University

Master's Degree, Nursing Leadership and Management · (2015 - 2017)

University of Santo Tomas

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Nursing Science · (1983 - 1987)